pressmart.net 2015-06-13

# ePublishing Company: Electronic Publishing Software / Solutions

### PRIVACY POLICY

Pressmart Media Limited ( **"Pressmart"** or **""We"** ) is committed in protecting the privacy of each individual of its subscriber community. This privacy policy ( **"Privacy Policy"** ) provides how We collect and make use of information provided by the subscriber ( **"You"** ) when You access the website of Pressmart ( **"Website"** ). Please note that this Privacy Policy applies only to Website owned by Pressmart and not to the websites of other companies or organizations to which We provide links.

This Privacy Policy applies only to information Pressmart collects about You as a subscriber of the Website. This Privacy Policy does not apply to information about You collected by Pressmart's affiliated providers or third party websites and offerings linked to or otherwise accessible from the Website. The information collected or received by Pressmart's affiliated providers and the third parties is subject to their own privacy policies.

**Information Collection and Use**

**Personal Information:** In general, We only collect personal information voluntarily provided by You, when You are:

1.      Registering on to the Website;

2.      Subscribing to services provided by Pressmart;

3.      Making inquiries about the services of Pressmart; or 

4.      Contacting Pressmart (including the customer service representatives or other employees) by email. 

In connection with these activities, We may collect personal information from You; including, but not limited to, your name, postal address, e-mail address, username, password, a picture of You, certain preference information (such as favorite URLs), whether or not You are a member of the Website, telephone number, fax number, company name, title, tax jurisdiction, credit card number and credit card expiration date.

**Non-personal information:** As a part of the standard operation of the Website, We may collect certain non-personal information from You including, but not limited to, your browser type, operating system, Internet service provider, IP address and the domain name from which You accessed the Website.

In addition, We may collect information about your browsing behavior, such as the date and time You visit the Website, the areas or pages of the Website that You visit, the amount of time You spend viewing the Website, the number of times You return to the Website and other click-stream data. We analyze the information to examine trends, administer the Website, track user's movement in the aggregate and gather broad demographic information for aggregate use.

**Use of Information**

We may use the information collected from You for any of the following purposes:

a.      to facilitate your use of the Website and for better understanding of needs of the subscribers; 

b.      to process and fulfill your orders for certain services; 

c.      to respond to your inquiries or requests for information about the services; 

d.      to send You information, promotional materials, and offers from Pressmart as well as from the subsidiaries and affiliates;

e.      to contact visitors of the Website when necessary; 

f.       to help You address your problems with the Website; 

g.      for proper administering of the Website; 

h.      to conduct internal reviews of the Website (e.g., to determine the number of visitors to specific pages within the Website); 

i.       registering on to the Website;

Non-personal information will be used for these purposes as well to monitor the Website and provide a greater online experience for the visitors. 

**Disclosure of Information**

We do not rent, sell or share personal information about You with other people or non-affiliated companies except to provide the services You have requested. When We have your permission, or under the following circumstances, We may transfer or otherwise disclose information collected from You to the following entities for the following purposes: 

a.      to the employees, independent contractors, subsidiaries, affiliates, consultants, business associates, service providers and suppliers of Pressmart, if the disclosure          will enable that entity to provide Pressmart with business, professional, or technical support

b.      to the employees, independent contractors, service providers and suppliers of Pressmart to fulfill your service request; 

c.      to the trusted partners who work on behalf of or with Pressmart under confidentiality agreements. These companies may use your personal information to help          Pressmart communicate with You about offers from Pressmart and the marketing partners. However, these companies do not have any independent right to          share this information;

d.      the advertisers which is inclusive of, but is not limited to, the financial service providers (such as banks, insurance agents, stock brokers and mortgage lenders) and          non-financial companies (such as stores, airlines, and software companies) of Pressmart; 

e.      when We determine that there has been a violation of the terms of use provided by Pressmart; and also to respond to judicial process and provide information to          law enforcement agencies or in connection with an investigation on matters related to public safety, as permitted by law;

f.      to share information in order to investigate, prevent, or take action regarding illegal activities, suspected fraud, situations involving potential threats to the physical          safety of any person, as otherwise required by law. 

g.      We transfer information about You to such other company when Presssmart is acquired by or merged with another company. In this event, We will notify You          before any information about You is transferred and becomes subject to a different privacy policy. 

**Confidentiality and Security**

a.      We limit access of personal information about You only to employees who We believe reasonably need to provide services to You or in order to do their jobs.

b.      We have physical, electronic and procedural safeguards that comply with legal regulations to protect personal information about You.

c.      To prevent unauthorized access, maintain data accuracy and ensure correct usage of information, We have put in place appropriate physical, electronic and          managerial procedures to safeguard and secure the information We collect online. 

d.      We have established sufficient safeguards to prevent unauthorized access to or misuse of your information, but cannot guarantee that your personally identifiable          information will never be disclosed in a manner inconsistent with this Privacy Policy (for example, as a result of unauthorized acts by third parties that violate          applicable law or the policies of the service and its affiliated providers).

**Third Party website**

The Website may contain links to other third party websites which may have privacy policies that differ from this Privacy Policy. We are not responsible for the activities and practices that take place on such websites. Accordingly, We recommend that You review the privacy policy posted on any website that You may access through the Website of Pressmart.

**Changes to this Privacy Policy**

Pressmart reserve the right, at its discretion, to change, modify, add or remove portions of this Privacy Policy at any time. We recommend that You revisit this Privacy Policy periodically to ensure that You are aware of the current privacy practices. Your continued use of services provided by Pressmart following any changes signifies your acceptance of these changes.
